who2.com 2011-11-02

# Who2.com - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, **Who2** provides this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way any information is collected and used. 

The **Who2** site is not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information not entered by visitors. Our site logs do generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as the number of hits and visits to our sites. We may use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. **Who2** may use non-identifying cookies to provide easier site navigation, access to forms, or to assist us in presenting the site to you. You can still use the **Who2** site if your browser is set to reject cookies. Our cookies do not generate personal data and are never tied to anything that could be used to identify you. 

**Who2** users may be offered the chance to receive newsletters or other regular updates. Such newsletters and materials are always of the "opt-in" variety, and users will not receive mail from us unless they indicate they desire it. 

Advertisements on **Who2** are organized and served by outside agencies. Those agencies may offer demographic surveys; participation in such surveys will be on an "opt-in" basis and therefore entirely voluntary on the part of our users. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Unless you consent, we will not use any personal information we receive from you for any purpose other than that for which it is submitted. We use personal information to reply to inquiries, handle complaints, or at times provide operational notices. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

We never sell or rent your personal information. 

**Who2** may release personal information to appropriate governmental authorities where such a release is required by law (for example, as the result of a subpoena), if your communication suggests possible harm to others. 

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13. Furthermore, we make every effort to provide a "family friendly" website which does not link to material that may be harmful to children. 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure our own database and the information we collect online. 

Any future additions to or alterations of our privacy policy will be posted publicly on this page. 

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us at: editorial@Who2.com. 

Date: 6 November 2010 

Jump to the [Who2 home page](http://www.who2.com/).
